I'll get coffee. Want anything, baby doll?
我要點咖啡外帶 洋娃娃，你也要嗎？
I'm fine. Thanks.
不用了，謝謝
I can't pull off "baby doll," can l?
我不能叫你洋娃娃吧
No,I think we learned that from the "sugar lips" incident.
對，從那次甜甜嘴事件 我們已經學到教訓了
I'll make some tea.
我去點茶來喝
How you doing,pumpkin?
小親親，你好嗎？
行不通
-So it's going well for you two? -I know. Really well.
你們倆看起來越來越好了呢 我知道，真的很好
I'm gonna ask Phoebe to move in with me.
其實我正想要菲比搬來我家
What do you think?
你覺得呢？
It's great! When will you ask her?
這真是太棒了 你何時要問她？
Tonight. But don't say anything.
今天晚上，你先別透露喔
I swear. I promise.
我發誓不說，人格擔保…
I'm so excited!
天啊，我超興奮的
But listen,do not get her flowers, okay?
我跟你說，記得不要送她花
Because she cries when they die. Then there's the whole funeral.
因為花謝了她會哭 還會幫花辦葬禮之類的
-I'll see you after work,sweetie. -Okay. Bye.
親愛的，下班後再見 好，再見
So, what movie should we see?
我們應該去看什麼電影？
Gary's gonna ask you to move in with him!
蓋瑞要請你搬去跟他住
What? Really?
什麼？真的嗎？
He made me promise not to tell, but I couldn't hold it in any longer!
他剛才在吧檯上跟我說的 他要我保證不會說出去 但我實在是憋不住
I can't believe this.
我不敢相信
Right? Because it's fast. Because it's so fast. It's fast.
對，因為太快了，太快…
Relax. It's Phoebe, not you.
別激動，是菲比，又不是你
Good for you, Phoebe. Way to go.
菲比，很厲害，有一套
No, but it is fast, isn't it?
不過真的是很快，對吧？
-I like him, but I'm not ready. -So,what are you gonna do?
我是很喜歡他沒錯 但我還沒有準備好要同居 那你打算怎麼辦？
I don't know. I'll just handle it. I'll ask you to talk to him!
不知道，兵來將擋 乾脆找你去和他說！
Me? Why me?
我？為何是我？
Because you are so afraid of commitment.
因為你怕死了給承諾
You talk to him. Make him scared like you, make him a man.
你去跟他說說 讓他跟你一樣怕 讓他成為一個…男人
I'll try, but I'm not sure what good it'd do.
我會去試試 但我不確定會多有用
I'm less afraid of commitment than I used to be.
因為比起以前 我現在已經不很害怕承諾了
That is so sweet.
真是太甜蜜了
Still terrified. I'll take care of it.
還是很怕 但我會處理，沒問題
The One With the Ball
本集播出：「同居大不行」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey,Ross,is Staten lsland really an island?
羅斯，斯塔頓島真的是島嗎？
That's why they call it Staten "lsland."
是啊，所以才叫斯塔頓「島」
Oh,I thought it was like Long lsland.
我還以為那跟長島一樣
Also an island.
長島也是島
-What time is it? -2:17.
幾點了？ 2點17分
We haven't dropped this ball for an hour.
你知道嗎？我們丟這個球連續一小時都沒有漏接落地
Are you serious?
你是認真的？
I realized it a half-hour ago, but I didn't say anything.
對，我半小時前就發現了 之所以沒說
I didn't wanna jinx it.
是怕壞了好事
We are pretty good at this.
我們還真會丟接球呢
We totally forgot about lunch.
我們完全忘了吃午餐
That's the first time I've ever missed a meal.
這是我第一次忘記吃飯
I think my pants are a little loose.
對，我的褲子都有點鬆了
Hey,you guys. Is Monica here?
嗨，摩妮卡在嗎？
I bought something. I'm not sure she'll like it.
我帶了東西回來 我不確定她會喜歡
It may seem crazy, but I've wanted this since I was a little girl.
聽起有點奇怪 那個東西我從小就想要了
You bought Shaun Cassidy!
你帶的是史恩卡希迪？ （歌手）
No. I wish!
不是，我也希望是
Okay,you ready?
你們準備好了沒？ 好了
那好
Check it out.
請看！
What is it?
那是啥啊？
What the hell is that?
什麼鬼東西？
It's a cat.
這是貓啊
That is not a cat!
這才不是貓
Yes,it is!
這就是貓啊
Why is it inside out?
它的皮怎麼翻出來了？
Excuse me!
幫幫忙
But this is a purebred, show-quality sphinx cat.
這可是展示級的 純種獅身人面貓
How much did you pay for that?
你花了多少錢買的？
It was extravagant, but I got a good deal.
有點奢侈 但我談到了很好的價錢
-How much? -Thousand bucks.
多少錢？ 一千美元
On a cat?
買一隻貓？
It's not a cat!
那才不是貓！
For a thousand dollars, you'd think at least it'd come with hair.
花一千元起碼也要有毛才對
Or something.
或是其他有的沒的
All right. Listen, ball boys.
你們這兩個玩球的給我聽好
My grandma had one when I was little. It was the sweetest thing.
我小時候祖母就養了這種貓 它們最討人喜歡了
It would sit in my lap and just purr all day long.
超可愛的，躺在我的膝蓋上 整天滿足地喵喵叫
I would drag a string and it would chase it.
我還會拿鞋帶在地上拖 讓它追著跑
Free cats do that too, you know.
不要錢的貓也會那樣
It's not a cat!
那才不是貓！
I'm really excited about this,okay? I don't care what you think.
反正我買得很興奮 我才不管你們怎麼想
I'm gonna set up a litter box for Mrs. Whiskerson.
我要去幫威絲克森太太 張羅出一個小貓砂盒
What am I gonna call her? Fluffy?
不然我要叫它「毛毛」嗎？
Do you wanna get something to eat, or see how long we can throw this ball?
你要去吃點東西嗎？ 還是要看我們能來回丟多久？
The ball thing.
繼續丟球 是喔
Wouldn't it be great if we could go for two hours without dropping it?
若我們連丟兩小時不落地 那樣是不是棒？
Yeah,it would!
對喔
Let's do it.
來吧 好
I have to pee.
我要尿尿
And Rachel's in the bathroom!
瑞秋卻在洗手間裡
Man,I didn't think we'd make it.
沒想到這樣也行
I know.
是啊
Don't switch hands, okay?
你別換手喔
Hey, ladies. What are you in here for?
小姐，你們在這裡幹嘛？
What are you doing here?
錢德，你來這裡幹嘛？
I am here to report a crime.
蓋瑞，我是來報案的 是嗎？
It's a crime that we don't spend time together.
我們倆不常聚在一起 是一種罪
What's up?
你有什麼事？
You're thinking about moving in with Phoebe, and I thought we should talk.
聽說你在考慮要菲比跟你同居 我心想我們或許應該聊聊
You know,man to...
男人…
...well,me.
跟我的對話
Sure,okay.
好啊，沒問題
Are you crazy?
你在發什麼神經？
Are you insane?
你瘋了？
If you live with Phoebe,you two are gonna be living together.
若你和菲比同居 你們兩個就會住在一起了
I considered that. It'd make me happy.
對，我考慮過了 我知道這會讓我快樂
-You mean scared. -No,I mean happy.
你是說害怕吧 不，我是說快樂
Scared happy.
害怕？快樂？
What are you doing?
錢德，你在幹嘛？
I'm trying to open your eyes!
我在讓你張開眼睛啊 你看不出來嗎？
If you live with Phoebe, she is always gonna be there.
若你和菲比同居 她就永遠都會在
You get home,she's there. You go to bed, she's there.
你回家會看到她 你上床也會看到她
You wake up and, oh, yes, she's there.
你起床呢？對，她還是在
I know. I can't wait!
我知道，我都等不及了
Were your parents happy or something?
你父母的婚姻很幸福吧？
I was lucky enough to find someone that I really love.
錢德，我看這件事的角度是 我很幸運能找到我的真愛
I just want to be around her as much as I can.
我想要盡量多跟她在一起
When you say it, it doesn't sound so scary.
怪了，這件事從你嘴裡說出來 感覺就沒那麼恐怖了
You know what I'm saying?
所以你懂我的意思吧？
Yeah,I think I do.
對，我想我懂
You know what?
這樣吧
Move in with her. Move in right now. Maybe I'll move in with Monica.
跟她同居 馬上就去跟她同居 或許我也應該和摩妮卡同居
No,it's too soon for you guys.
不成，你們不能操之過及
You're right about that.
是啊，你說的對
When they found the remains of the Mesozoic mastodon...
他們找到中生代乳齒象化石
...they discovered what appeared to be the remains...
卻在嘴部發現到
...of a Paleozoic amphibian in its jaws.
類似古生代兩棲類的構造
How did it get there?
怎麼會牛頭不對馬嘴？
Maybe this should be more of a quiet game.
或許這個遊戲應該安靜一點
Hey,guys.
嗨 嗨
I left my watch here last night.
我昨晚把手錶放在櫃子上
-lt was here. Where is it? -I don't know.
本來還在這裡，到哪兒去了？ 我不知道
I'm late for work.
別鬧了，我上班快遲到了
How do you know? You don't have a watch.
你怎麼知道？你又沒戴表
Can you stop throwing the ball for one minute and help me find it?
能不能停一下再丟球 先幫我找表？
Oh, I don't know.... Yeah,can't do it.
不知道，沒辦法喔
-What? -Do not drop that ball.
怎樣啦？怎樣都好 千萬別把球掉地上
We haven't dropped it in....
我們保持球不落地已經…
Two hours,27 minutes.
2小時27分鐘
Really?
真的啊？
I won't make it in to work today.
我今天沒辦法去上班
I don't feel very good.
我人不太舒服
漂亮！
For a second, I thought I was feeling better, but I'm not.
我剛才突然覺得自己好多了 但其實沒有
Hey, Rach.
瑞秋 嗨
Check it out. Almost three hours without dropping it.
快來看，球不落地接近三小時
Congratulations. That's quite a waste of time.
恭喜了，真是浪費時間
You have scratches all over you.
你身上都是抓痕，怎麼了？
Well,it's my cat.
是我的貓
-Oh,I got a cat. -I don't want a cat!
對了，我養了一隻貓 我不想養貓
Don't worry,it's not a cat.
別擔心，那不是貓 沒錯
You guys,this cat is nothing like my grandmother's cat.
這隻貓跟我祖母養過的貓 完全不一樣
It's not sweet. It's not cute.
既不討人喜歡，也不可愛
I dragged a string,and it flipped out and scratched the hell out of me.
我在地上拉著線逗它玩 它竟然發飆 把我抓得亂七八糟
I know this sounds crazy, but every time this cat hisses at me...
我知道這聽來很瘋狂 但我發誓 這隻貓每次噓我的時候
...I know it's saying,"Rachel!"
我知道它都在說「瑞秋」
Doesn't sound as crazy as paying $1000 for a cat.
花一千買美元買一隻貓 比剛才那些話更瘋狂
You paid $1000 for a cat when you owe me $300?
你欠我三百美元不還 還拿一千美元去買貓？
Well,I was gonna let you play with it.
我本來打算讓你跟它玩的
「中央咖啡館」
Did you talk to Gary about moving in?
你跟蓋瑞聊過同居的事沒？
I think you should do it.
聊過了，我覺得你應該答應
He's a great guy and he loves you a lot. You are a very lucky lady.
他很棒，他也很愛你 你非常幸運
You are useless!
你真沒用
Freaking out about commitment is the one thing you can do...
害怕承諾是你唯一會做的事
...and you can't even do that right!
你竟然連那件事都做不好！ 天啊
Sorry. If he asked me, I'd move in with him.
抱歉 換做我都願意和他同居
Get out of here,good-for-nothing.
窩囊廢，你滾吧
Hey,Chandler.
錢德
Hey,Gar.
蓋瑞
Hey,sweetie.
親愛的
Can I talk to you for a second?
能不能先聊一下？ 好啊
You look pretty today.
你今天很美
Thanks. Okay.
謝謝，好吧
Here's the thing.
是這樣的
I really want this relationship to move forward.
我很想讓這段關係更進一步
If you're not moving forward, you're moving backwards.
因為不進則退
No, if you're not moving forward, you're staying still.
不對，那不是真的 如果不進，就是靜止不動
And staying still is good. Watch this.
靜止不動是很好的，你看
菲比 是
I want you to move in with me.
我要你搬來一起住
That is so sweet.
那真是太甜蜜了
But don't you think it's too soon?
但你不覺得太快了些嗎？
There's so much we don't know about each other.
我們彼此還有太多地方不瞭解
Okay. I get it.
好吧，我懂了
I don't want us to jump into something that we're not ready for.
我只是不希望我們操之過急 你懂吧？
I don't want to mess up what we have.
我不想搞砸我們現在的一切
I'm worried it's gonna be a big mistake.
我擔心同居會鑄成大錯
是啊
Which is why my answer is yes!
所以我的答案是我答應
Really?
真的嗎？
You're so happy.
我好快樂
Monica, stop throwing it so hard!
摩妮卡，別丟那麼大力！
We're on the same team!
我們是同一隊
You guys have been doing this for four hours?
四個小時？ 你們就這樣丟了四小時？
That's right,baby.
寶貝，沒錯
-All right. Let me in. -No,no! Don't do it!
好，讓我加入 不行！…
What?
什麼？
He's a dropper.
他是掉球大王
Oh,yeah. That's right!
對，沒錯！
I'm not a dropper!
我才不是掉球大王
It's really a three-person game, you know?
這其實是三個人的遊戲
It's throwing and catching.
還不就是你丟我接
All right.
好吧
Oh,it's so hard.
好大力喔
Don't worry,guys. It's not a cat.
別緊張，那不是貓喔
Oh,good God!
我的…天啊
I give up. I don't know what I'm gonna do with this thing.
我放棄了 我不知道要怎麼處理
Baking it didn't help?
送它進烤箱也沒用？
Take it back to where you got it.
把它送回你買的地方呢？
I tried. They won't take her back.
我試過了，他們不收
Maybe that's because she's a minion of the Antichrist.
或許是因為它是反基督的爪牙
Why won't they take it?
瑞秋，店家為什麼不收？
They said they would only give me store credit.
他們說要收回可以 但只退我店裡的購物券
What am I gonna do? Get 1000 regular cats?
我要拿來買什麼？ 一千隻普通的貓不成？
You said it was a show cat. Why don't you show it,win some prize money.
你不是說這是展示貓嗎？ 那就帶去比賽拿獎品啊
Those shows cost a hundred bucks to enter, and all you win are these ribbons...
參加貓展要先繳一百美元 贏來的東西
...which technically belong to the damn cat.
還不是都歸這死貓所有
You can keep it until you find out what to do with it.
不然你先留著羅 等到你找到處理的方法
That's not the point. I'm out $1000...
不行，那不是重點 我破費一千美元
...I'm all scratched up...
搞得全身都是抓痕
...and I'm stuck with this stupid cat that looks like a hand!
還跟長得像手的蠢貓困在一起
Oh,my God!
天啊
The cat's made my eyes water. Don't throw it to me!
那隻貓害我流眼淚了 別丟球給我！
My vision's been compromised!
我的視力被連累到了
Oh,God! Okay.
天啊，好了…
It's okay. Man,that was close.
現在好了，真是驚險
Yeah,you almost overreacted to something.
是啊，你的反應也太大了點
-We have great news. -We're moving in together. Yay!
我們有個好消息 我們要同居了，是不是很棒？
Congratulations.
恭喜…
-I'm so excited! -So am l.
是啊 我好興奮 我也是
You're not more excited than I am. No way. I'm the most excited.
你才沒有我興奮，不可能 我是最興奮的
See you at the station later.
好，晚點在局裡見
I'll see you later. Don't forget about the moving-in!
好，晚點見 別忘了同居的事喔
So you're moving in with him?
你要搬去跟他住，怎麼了？
I couldn't tell him no. He got so sad. Maybe it'll be all right.
我不忍心拒絕他 看他傷心成那樣 或許不會有事的
I do like him a lot...
我真的很喜歡他
...and probably do it eventually,anyway.
同居八成也是遲早的事
Plus,think of all the money I'll save on stamps.
想想也可以省下不少郵票錢
Do you write him a lot?
怎麼著？你常寫信給他？
I heard when people live together...
不是，只是我聽說同居的人
...they split the cost of stamps,don't they?
會分擔郵票的費用，不是嗎？
-Yeah,yeah. -That's right.
是啊，沒錯…
Sorry,the oven mitts really freaked me out.
抱歉，耐熱手套嚇了我一跳
Hey,honey.
親愛的
Did you find any apartments in Brooklyn Heights?
你找到公寓沒？ 布魯克林高地有嗎？
No, nothing.
不，沒找到
-Oh, really? -Yeah.
真的？ 是啊
-Nothing at all? -No.
一間都沒有？ 沒有
If something opens up,we'll move in. If it has a pool. I need a pool.
只要有公寓招租 我們馬上搬進去 不過要有附泳池的 我需要泳池
Can I talk to you?
菲比，可以跟你聊一下嗎？
Take a seat.
請坐 好
You okay?
你沒事吧？
You feel all right?
還好吧？
I feel great, because we're moving in together.
我很好啊，因為我們要同居了
So you....
那麼...
You checked the paper for listings in Brooklyn Heights,right?
報上布魯克林高地的租屋廣告 你都看過了？
You checked the Post?
郵報你有查過嗎？
Yeah,there was nothing.
有啊，啥都沒有
-Can I get some water? -ln a minute.
我能喝點水嗎？ 等一下
You checked today's Post?
你查過今天的郵報嗎？
Yeah,today's.
對，我是看今天的
Because this is today's Post.
這是今天的郵報
And these are the listings I found.
我找到了這些租屋廣告
Brooklyn Heights, two bedrooms. Brooklyn Heights, one bedroom.
布魯克林高地，兩房 布魯克林高地，一房
Brooklyn Heights,Brooklyn Heights, Brooklyn Heights!
布魯克林高地地區…
Oh,are these for rent? I thought people were just bragging.
這些是要租的嗎？我以為他們是在 炫耀自己的房子有多棒
Let me tell you what's going on here.
我來告訴你我的想法
Don't look at the table. Look at me.
不要看桌子，看著我
Somebody asked someone to move in with him.
一個男生要求一個女生同居
Someone said yes, but now she has doubts...
女生本來說好，現在反悔了
...because things are moving too fast. Does that sound possible?
因為女生覺得這樣太快了 你覺得是不是這樣？
Yes,fine! I am someone!
對！…好，我就是那個女生
You want me to say it? I have doubts!
你要我說老實話？ 對，我是不確定
I'm sorry!
對不起
菲比？
It's okay that you feel this way.
你有這種感覺也沒關係
It is soon, and there's things we don't know about each other.
這真的是很快 我們對彼此有許多地方不瞭解
Everything I know about you, I really like.
我只是覺得 我知道的你，我都很喜歡
Things I don't know, I'll learn in a place with our names on the mailbox.
我還不知道的你 就等同居後再慢慢瞭解
That's so sweet.
那樣好甜蜜喔
But if it's too soon for you, we don't have to do it.
不過如果你覺得這樣太快 我剛才說的可以慢慢再來 不用趕著現在就同居
I want you to be happy.
我只想要你快樂
Living with you would make me happy.
跟你同居會讓我快樂的
You don't have to say that.
菲比，你不用那樣說
I want to live with you. I want to move in with you.
不，我很想跟你住在一起 我要跟你同居
Are you sure?
你確定？
Definitely,yes! Let's live in an apartment we both live in.
對，百分之百確定！ 我們一起住在公寓同居吧
Oh,that's great.
太好了
Oh,wait, one sec.
等等…
Hey,you! Behind the glass. Who are you looking at?
鏡子後面的人 你看什麼看！
I always wanted to say that every time I was in these rooms, which was never.
我每次進來這種房間 都想說這句話 雖然我從沒進來過
Show cat!
展示貓
Quality show cat!
高級的展示貓
-Show cat! -Oh,my God!
展示貓 天啊
What's wrong with your baby?
你的寶寶怎麼了？
That's not a baby. That's a cat.
這不是寶寶，這是貓
-It's creepy-looking. -Oh,no.
長得還真嚇人 不
It's actually very sweet. It's very sweet. Look.
它其實很討人喜歡的… 不信你看
Yeah. Do you want it?
你要不要？
No,I hate cats.
不了，我恨貓
Then what are you doing to me?
那你幹嘛跟我扯半天？
Get out of here,all right? Move on!
滾吧，繼續走你的路
What an unusual cat.
這隻貓真不尋常
Yes,thank you! Exactly. You want it?
是的，謝謝你 真的是這樣，你要嗎?
Maybe.
有可能
I was thinking about getting a cat from the shelter,but....
我考慮要養貓 我正好要去流浪動物之家…
-Okay. Why not? -Oh,terrific! That'll be $2,000.
好吧，就它了 太好了，總共是兩千美元
-What? -Okay,1000.
什麼？ 好吧，一千
Didn't you want me to adopt your cat?
我以為你是要我認養你的貓
I do,but you'll have to look at this as more of an investment than a cat.
是啊，不過這不只是貓 更是一項投資
Okay,yeah. I just wanted a cat.
好吧，我要的只是貓
Obviously,you know how to haggle, so I won't try and take you on.
你顯然是殺價高手 所以我就不唬弄你了
So $800,and I don't call the cops, because you are robbing me blind!
算你八百，我也不報警了 因為你這根本是搶劫
Blind! Just take the cat. Leave the money. Run away!
把錢留下，貓帶走 溜之大吉吧…
Run away. Damn it!
快走吧 可惡！
Can't you at least smile or something?
死貓，你起碼也笑一下嘛
Did anybody just hear that? Anybody?
有沒有人聽到？誰聽到了？
-I'm starving. -Come on,guys. Suck it up!
我餓死了 你們振作一點
We're closing in on 10 hours.
就快達成連續十小時了
It's gut-check time!
這是比毅力的時刻
I don't know who made you the boss. We invented this game.
怎麼變成是你當老大？ 這遊戲是我們發明的
I made this game what it is!
幫幫忙，這遊戲是因為我 才有現在的局面
Not fun anymore?
不再好玩的局面？
I'm still hungry.
我還是很餓
There's pizza at my place. We can eat with one hand. Are you with me?
好吧，我家還有一點比薩 你們可以用一手吃吧？ 要不要？
-I am. -All right,let's go! Come on!
我要 好，我們走…
Let's go, Team Monica!
摩妮卡大隊，走羅
We can work out the name later.
好啦，隊名等一下再討論
What is your cat doing in my bowl?
瑞秋，你的貓在我碗裡幹嘛？
I'm defrosting a chicken.
不是啦，我在解凍雞肉
I sold Mrs. Whiskerson.
我把威絲克森太太賣掉了
Thank God!
謝天謝地
-Get your money back? -Yeah,$1500.
你的錢拿回來沒？ 有，一千五百美元
You made a profit?
哇，你還有賺耶
I just came for the red velvet pillow.
我是來拿紅絲絨枕頭的
-There you go. -Thanks,Rachel.
在這裡 瑞秋，謝了
Don't forget, you can come visit her anytime.
別忘了，你隨時可以來看它
Oh, good. Great. I'll keep that in mind.
好…我會記得的
So is this some kind of snake or something?
這是啥？某種蛇嗎？
I like waking up with you.
我真喜歡和你一起醒來
I like waking up with you too.
我也是
Oh, it's such a beautiful morning.
今天早上真美
I could stay here all day.
我可以在床上待一整天
That would be great.
那樣不錯
-We could have breakfast in bed. -Wait,just a second.
我們可以在床上吃早餐 等等 好
Oh,no.
不會吧
All right. Come on, Monica! Look alive. Come on!
來，摩妮卡，活力點…
Oh,I was having the best dream.
我剛才做了最棒的夢
-What? -I dreamed I was drowning...
什麼夢？ 我夢到自己溺水
...and not throwing this ball.
不用再丟這顆球了
Oh, good. You're all up.
很好，你們都起床了
It's 6:00 in the morning. Why aren't you at Gary's?
菲比，現在才早上六點 你怎麼沒在蓋瑞那裡？
-Oh, yeah. That's over. -What?
對，結束了 什麼？
Gary's such a great guy. You can work it out.
別這樣，蓋瑞這麼好 有什麼問題都能解決的
-He shot a bird. -That is over.
他開槍殺了一隻鳥 結束了
-I'm sorry. -That's terrible.
太糟糕了…我很遺憾…
Are you okay?
菲比，你還好吧？
I'll be all right.
對…我不會有事的
Here,Phoebe.
菲比，接住
I don't feel like playing.
我不太想玩球
It's okay. It's okay.
沒事…
It didn't happen. No one needs to know.
就當沒發生這件事 沒必要讓別人知道
She's not an official ball player.
菲比又不是正式的隊員
Only official ball players can drop the ball.
正式隊員掉球才算數
-Come on. -Let's go.
算了…我好餓…
You wanna get breakfast?
菲比，要吃早餐嗎？
Okay, let's race!
好，我們來賽跑
First one there wins.
最先到的贏
You guys wanna eat here?
你們要在這裡吃嗎？
That was great,huh?
在這裡就好
Can you believe how long we threw it?
真不敢相信我們丟了那麼久
It is amazing it lasted that long.
是啊，撐了那麼久 真的很不可思議
My arm is killing me.
是啊，我的手臂酸死了
No, I meant with the dropper over here.
不是，我是說有掉球高手在 還能那麼久
How did I get this reputation as a dropper?
「掉球高手」這稱號 怎麼會落到我頭上？
I am anything but a dropper.
我再怎麼說也不是掉球高手
Ross!
羅斯…